Finding aid for the Richard Baum papers, 1961-2012 LSC.2272
UCLA Library Special Collections
Richard Baum papers
1961-2012
UCLA Library Special Collections
Baum, Richard
LSC.2272
8.8 linear feet (19 document boxes, 1 record carton, 1 shoe box)
The collection consists of materials related to the career of UCLA professor of Political Science, US policy advisor, and China scholar Richard Baum. Baum was founder of the listserv Chinapol and was an influential authority on contemporary Chinese politics who authored more than 50 scholarly studies and six books. The materials include correspondence, conference files, Baum's writings, course materials, and recordings of Baum's lectures.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This collection contains processed audiovisual materials. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Karin Joffe, 2013.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9976870473606533
Biography/History
Richard Baum was born in Los Angeles, CA on July 8, 1940. Baum Studied political science at UCLA, receiving his bachelor's degree in 1962. Baum continued his political science studies at UC Berkeley, receiving his master's degree in 1963 and his doctorate in 1970. Baum traveled to Taiwan in 1967 to study Mandarin while working towards his doctorate degree. It was during this trip that Baum discovered classified materials documenting activities at the highest levels of the Chinese Communist Party (CCP). Baum launched into his scholarly career when he made unauthorized copies of these documents and used the materials to write an analysis of the conflicts between Chairman Mao's Cultural Revolution and the interests of the CCP.
Baum began teaching Political Science at UCLA in 1968 and continued his career there for 44 years. While at UCLA, Baum was also the director of the Center for Chinese Studies from 1999 until 2005. Throughout his career, Baum was an influential authority on contemporary Chinese politics, serving as a popular media commentator and a high-level U.S. policy advisor. Baum served on the editorial boards for numerous scholarly journals, including the US-China Institute and China Quarterly. Baum was the founder of Chinapol, an extensive listserv used by scholars, officials, and journalist to discuss Chinese politics. Additionally, Baum authored more than 50 scholarly studies and six books, including Burying Mao: Chinese Politics in the Age of Deng Xiaoping. Baum died in Los Angeles, California on December 14, 2012.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of materials related to the career of professor, advisor, and China scholar Richard Baum. The materials include correspondence, conference files, Baum's writings, course materials, and recordings of Baum's lectures. The collection relates to Baum's teaching and directing roles at UCLA, high-level U.S. policy advising, trips to China, speaking engagements, and conference presentations. Many notes in this collection include the intricate mandala doodles of Baum.
Organization and Arrangement
This collection has been arranged in the following series:
Series 1: Professional Files, 1961-2012
Subseries 1.1: Correspondence
Subseries 1.2: Conference Files
Subseries 1.3: Faculty Papers
Subseries 1.4: Professional Activities Files
Subseries 1.5: Writings
Series 2: Recorded Lectures and Interviews, 1972-1996
University of California, Los Angeles. Department of Political Science--Faculty -- Archives; Baum, Richard -- Archives
- Series 1: Professional Files, 1961-2012
  Scope and Content
  This series contains correspondence, conference files, course materials, professional activities files, and writings.
  - 1.1: Correspondence, 1961-2007
    Organization and Arrangement
    This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    Correspondence includes personal letters exchanged between students and colleagues, and professional communications with UCLA faculty, White House departments, the CIA, US Embassies and broadcasting stations. Also included are documents requesting Baums' participation in interviews and journals.
    - Correspondence, 1960 - 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1960 - 1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1970 - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Chinese Visitors and Scholars, 1980 - 1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1980 - 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - UCLA Correspondence, 1982 - 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1983 - 1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1983 - 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1990 - 1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: International Institute of Strategic Studies, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1997 - 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 2001 - 2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1.2: Conference Files, 1964-2005
    The conference files contain scholarly papers, handouts, and schedules for numerous events including those sponsored by the Aspen Institute, the Pacific Rim Research Studies, and the RAND Corporation.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by conference title.
    - Allen Whiting Symposium, 2000 - 2001 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Asia Center, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Asia Institute, 2002 - 2004 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Aspen Institute, 2003 - 2004 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Aspen Institute, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Berkeley Pacific Rim Conference, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - CIA China Conference, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - CIA Chinese Economy Report, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Communication and Cultural Change in China" East-West Center Conference, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Conference on World Affairs, 1993 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Conference on World Affairs, 1994 - 2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - China Reform Forum: RAND 7th Annual Conference, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Doing Business with China Conference, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Education Abroad Program China Trip, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Education Abroad Program - Honk Kong Symposium, 1997 - 1999 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Harvard Conferences, 1989 - 1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Harvard Conference "Economic Reform in China", 1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Hoover Institution "Elections in Taiwan, Hong Kong and Mainland China" Conference, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Homeokinetics Conference, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - International Institute of Strategic Studies: China Rising Conference, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - International Institute of Strategic Studies: China After 16th Party Congress Conference, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - International China Conference at Schloss Reisenburg, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Joint Committee in Chinese Studies Conference: To Reform the Chinese Political Order, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Lingnan College Reform Cycles Conference, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Meiji University - UCLA Research Project, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities Research Conference, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Council Conferences, 1997 - 2002 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Political Interest in the People's Republic of China, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - "People's Republic of China After the 15th Party Congress", 1997 - 1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - RAND-China Reform Conference, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Seminar: Local Governance in India and China, 2001 - 2003 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Social Science Research Center - American Council of Learned Societies Conference, 1982 - 1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Stanford Workshop on Technological Change in China, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Technology and Communist Culture Conference, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - UC San Diego Conference: Global Issues in German-American Partnership, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - UCLA Asia Leadership Council, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - UCLA Center for Chinese Studies Conference, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - UCLA China Symposium, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Urchfront Conference: Contemporary China Institute, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - US-China Conference, 1999 - 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - US-China Relations Conference, Pomona, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Various Conferences, 2002 - 2008 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Wilson Center, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1.3: Faculty papers, 1964-2005
    The faculty papers include syllabi, teaching materials, papers documenting departmental activities, curriculum planning, and materials relating to Baum's role as Director for the Center for Chinese Studies.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically.
    - American Council of Learned Societies Applications, 1983 - 1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Center for Chinese Studies UCLA, 1987 - 2005 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Center for Chinese Studies UCLA, 1984 - 1988 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Computing, 1984 - 1986 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Computing, 1984 - 1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Computing, 1984 - 1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Education Abroad Program Selection Committee, 1991 - 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Exchange Program, 1990 - 1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Council Department Self-Review, 1990 - 1999 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Human Social Systems, 1983 - 1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Human Social Systems, 1990 - 1999 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Rim Studies UCLA, 1987 - 1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Social Science Course Readings, 1987 - 1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Political Science Course Reader, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Political Science Department UCLA, 1983 - 1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Re-entry of Chinese Scholars, 1988 - 1989 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - UCLA China Connection, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - UCLA Zhong Shan Joint Seminar, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - UCLA China Exchange, 1978 - 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - UCLA Research Grants, 1983 - 2002 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1.4: Professional Activities Files, 1973-2005
    Of his numerous professional associations, the collection contains the most files on Baum's association with the Henry Luce Foundation and the Asia Society's China Council. It also includes a large file on his involvement with a documentary film on China by Paula Haller on which he acted as consultant. His various trips to China for research are also documented thoroughly in this subseries. Please note that box 17 contains photographic negatives and their prints.
    This subseries is arranged by topic, maintaining the original organizational order of this collection.
    - Speaking Engagements, 1978 - 1986 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Speaking Engagements, 1978 - 1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Speaking Events, 1985 - 2005 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - China Lectures, 1999 - 2012 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - China Lectures, 1999 - 2012 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - China Lectures, 1973 - 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Lectures, Seminars, Briefings, 1993 - 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Sister City Association, 1979 - 1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - International Business Education and Research Pacific Rim Management Program, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Peking University Research Center, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Research Files, 1982 - 1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Notes on Needham - Storer, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Pearl Cruise Lectures, 1988 - 1995 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Paula Haller Film Project, 1980 - 1984 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Camp David Briefing, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Joint Center for International Studies, 2002 - 2005 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Sanchuan Development Association, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - International Studies and Overseas Programs, 1999 - 2002 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Mapping Local Governance Workshop, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Democracy: The Bridge Between China and Taiwan Conference, 1998 - 2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - David Chu Criticism, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Pacific Rim Executive Committee, 1997 - 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Council Study Groups, 2000 - 2003 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Pacific Council China Study Group, 1996 - 2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Princeton Visiting Faculty Position, 1996 - 2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Chinese Visiting Delegations, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Henry Luce Foundation, 1976 - 1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Henry Luce Foundation, 1976 - 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Henry Luce Foundation, 1976 - 1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Henry Luce Foundation proposed, 1976 - 1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Henry Luce Foundation, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Henry Luce Foundation, 1981 - 1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - China Council, 1970 - 1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - China Council, 1970 - 1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - China Council, 1970 - 1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - China Council, 1970 - 1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - China Council, 1970 - 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - China Relations Committee, 1979 - 1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Trade with China, 1972 - 1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Technology Transfer Project, 1976 - 1978 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - China Trip, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - China Trip, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - China Trip, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - China Trip, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - China Trip: Photographic Prints and Negatives, 1975; Contains Photographic negatives and their prints. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - China Trip, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - China Trip, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - China Trip, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - China Trip, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Engineering Education Delegation, 1978 - 1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Engineering Education Delegation, 1978 - 1979 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Engineering Education Delegation, 1978 - 1979 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Engineering Education Delegation, 1978 - 1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Engineering Education Delegation: Notes, 1978 - 1979 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Chinese Language Materials, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Notes on Industrial Work, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Unisort Card Master Index, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Chinese Language Notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Chinese Language Notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Chinese Language Notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Hong Kong Research Files, 1995 - 2000 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Hong Kong Transition, 1992 - 1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Chinese Communism and Politics, 1952 - 1953 (Box 19)
      Bound manuscripts.
  - 1.5: Writings, 1962-2012
    A draft of China Watcher: Confessions of a Peking Tom is included in the writings, along with drafts of his published scholarly papers.
    This subseries is arranged chronologically by focused projects and collections of short form essays.
    - Drafts of "Regulations to Work in Rural People's Communes", 1961 - 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Draft of "Maoism and the Chinese Industrial Revolution", 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Drafts of "Technology and Social Change in Chinese Industry", 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Drafts of "Diabolus Ex Machina", 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Draft of "Latent Interest in Chinese Industrial Enterprises", 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Draft of "Cultural Constraints on the Modernization of Chinese Science", 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Draft of "Science, Bureaucracy, and the Four Modernizations", 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Draft of "The Gang of Four: Political Trial or Rule of Law for China?", 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Draft of "Ritual and Rationality: The origins of Bureaucratic Culture in Ancient China", 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Draft of "MGI1 and Incipient Pluralism in Post-Mao China", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Country Monitory Service Report: Taiwan, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Physical Oriented Foundations for a Unified Social Science, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - "Burying Mao" Book Project, 1991 - 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Draft of "China's Political Landscape: The Current Scene", 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Draft of "Prospects for Political Stability in Post-Deng China", 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Drafts of "China After Deng: Ten Scenarios in Search of Reality", 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Drafts of "The 'State of the State' in Post-Reform China", 1996 - 2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Draft of "The 15th Party Congress", 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Drafts of "Bringing China In", 1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Drafts of "Britain's 'Betrayal' of Hong Kong: A Second Look", 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Drafts of "China and the Forces of Globalization", 1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Draft of " Democracy Deformed: Hong Kong's 1998 Legislative Elections... And Beyond", 1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Draft of "Enter the Dragon: China's Courtship of Hong Kong", 1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Draft of "From 'Strategic Partners' to 'Strategic Competitors': George W. Bush and the Politics of U.S. China Policy", 2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Draft of "To Reform or to Muddle Through? The Challenges Facing China's Fourth Generation", 2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Draft of "Civil Society Revisited" with review, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Draft of "Present Nationalism and Communist Power", 2003 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Draft of "The Tawain-China Tangle: Divided Sovereignty in the Age of Globalization", 2003 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Draft of "Systemic Stresses and Political Chaos" The Road Ahead", 2003 - 2004 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Drafts of "The Origin of Polities: A Preliminary Inquiry into the Evolution of Command and Control in Human Collectivities", 2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Draft for "Uncertain Prospects for Political Reform in China", 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Draft of "The Limits of Consultative Leninism", 2006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Draft of "The Urgent Need for Political Reform", 2006 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Draft of "China Watcher" part 1, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Draft of "China Watcher" part 2, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Draft of "China Watcher" part 3, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Draft of "Civil Society in Self-Defense: The Struggle Aginst National Security Legislation in Hong Kong", 2007 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Draft of "The U.S.-China-Taiwan Triangle: New Hope for Old Antagonism?", 2008 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Draft of "Political Implications of China's Information Revolution: The Media, Its Minders, and Their Message", 2009 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - The Basics of Chinapol, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Draft of "The Limits of Authoritarian Resilience", 2014 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - UC Berkeley Graduate Writings part 1, 1962 - 1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - UC Berkeley Graduate Writings part 2, 1962 - 1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - China Working Papers, Research and Presentation, 1975 - 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Essays on American Perspectives of China, 1978 - 2010 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Research Notes, 1982 - 2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Various Drafts and Handwritten Notes, 1986 - 1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Short Essays, 1989 - 2008 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Presentations, 1989 - 2012 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Essays on Liberalization of China, 1994 - 2012 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Effects of Globalization on Self-Determination, 1997 - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Series 2: Recorded Lectures and Interviews, 1972-1996
  This series contains audio and visual recordings of Baum's lectures and interviews. The series also contains a set of cassette tapes recording the lectures of an Honor's Collegium course, which Baum was one of the lecturers. Video materials include two video reels documenting a KCET interview about Richard Nixon's visit to China and three reels recording a lecture by Baum titled: "A Briefing on Post-Mao China."
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Contains audio cassette tapes, video tape reels, and 7" audio reels. Use of audio and/or moving image material requires production of use copies. Advance notice is required for use. Please contact Library Special Collections reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - China Watch: Discussion of Nixon's Visit to China: KCET Channel 28 Part 1, February 21, 1972 (Box 20)
    Sony Helical Scan 1/2" reel to reel magnetic audio tape; slightly warped and crinkled.
  - China Watch: Discussion of Nixon's Visit to China: KCET Channel 28 Part 2, February 21, 1972 (Box 20)
    Sony Helical Scan 1/2" reel to reel magnetic audio tape; Slightly warped and crinkled.
  - A Briefing on Post-Mao China part 1, March 5, 1979 (Box 20)
    U-Matic Video Cassette (Memorex); 1 hour; Black and white; Mono audio; Master.
  - A Briefing on Post-Mao China part 2, March 5, 1979 (Box 20)
    U-Matic Video Cassette (Scotch); 1 hour; Crystallization appearing on tapes edges - possible sticky shed syndrome.
  - A Briefing on Post-Mao China part 3, March 5, 1979 (Box 20)
    U-Matic Video Cassette (Memorex); 1 hour; Black and white; Mono audio; Master; Crystallization appearing on tapes edges - possible sticky shed syndrome.
  - Struggle for China, 1987 (Box 20)
    VHS Tape; 55 minutes.
  - Struggle for China, November 5, 1987 (Box 20)
    U-Matic Video Cassette (Sony).
  - China Tomorrow: United States Air Force Academy Lecture, 1981 (Box 20)
    1/4" reel to reel magnetic audio tape; 3 3/4 recording speed; 1 hour.
  - China on the Move: United States Air Force Academy Lecture, February 13, 1981 (Box 20)
    1/4" reel to reel magnetic audio tape; Slightly warped and crinkled; 3 3/4 recording speed; 1 hour.
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 1 Professor Richard Baum, September 29, 1988 (Box 21)
    Cassette Tape
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 2, not dated (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 3 Professor Iberall, October 6, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 4 Chemical Foundations Professor Iberall, October 11, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 5 Professor Goldberg, October 13, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 6 Biology Professor Goldberg, October 18, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 7 Ethology Doug White, October 20, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 8 Ethology Doug White, October 25, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 9 Anthropology Professor Moore, October 27, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 10 A. Moore, November 1, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 11 Economics Professor Day, November 3, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 12 Economics Professor Day, November 8, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 13 Politics Professor Richard Baum, Novemeber 10, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 14 Politics Professor Richard Baum, November 15, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 15 Civilizations Professor Wilkinson, November 12, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 16 Civilizations Professor Wilkinson, November 22, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Lecture 18 Law Paul Wolmuth, December 1, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Honors Collegium 74: Course Evaluation, December 6, 1988 (Box 21)